Thanks for looking!
Good evening.
Yes, I mean...
I don't know if it's early.
I'm not sure if it's early or not.
Let's see, Sakurai Emma Kojin
Showroom Kojin Aka
We are pleased to announce the opening of our new showroom!
Congratulations!
What's this?
Wow, wow, wow!
I'm a shrimp.
This is the first time I'm doing it alone, so
I'm a little nervous.
I'm a little bit nervous, but I'm hoping that I'll be able to talk
I'd like to talk about a lot of things.
This is...
It's difficult.
There's a lot of things
Because there are things that touch you.
It's difficult, isn't it?
This one.
How many people are watching now? I wonder...
I don't know.
Great, great, great, great, great, great, great, great, great, great, great, great.
Great, great, great, great, great, great, great, great, great, great.
That was fast, fast, fast.
I don't know...
Thank you.
Thank you for what?
Thank you for everything.
What do you mean?
I don't know.Well, I don't know.
Well, as far as what I want to talk about...
Well, live music.
The spring tour.
"Lucky Fest.
My birthday party...
I'd like to talk about a lot of things.
But...
I can't decide what to do with my bangs today.
I don't know...
Well...
First of all...
The spring tour.
100%.
Wism...
The day before yesterday?
I lied.
On the 16th.
The 16th.
Well...
I wrote about it on my blog.
How did everyone do?
Some of you have already passed through the entire program.
I'm very grateful.
How was it? Everyone. It was 100% without a doubt.
Yes, indeed, indeed.
In the beginning, we were just trying hard not to make any mistakes in the dance, or in the formation, or in the dance,
But towards the end, it was getting better and better,
Oh, my stars! Thank you very much.
I started to enjoy it more and more. I was so excited to see you and YoonA talking about it. Yuna and I were saying that we were really enjoying the show.
I was really enjoying 100% at the end. I was.
And so was everyone else. But you were having fun too, right?
You looked like you were having a great time.
You looked like you were having fun.
Mm-hmm.Hmmm.
Thank you, Markon Ikuko. Stars, shooting stars. It's now an Emma star.
Oh, thank you already. I'm glad. It's something, you know...
Last week, after the fall was over...
I wanted to hear your thoughts on the story, so I put up a column for you to write your comments.
I wanted to hear what people thought about the story, so I added a column for people to write in,
I was also very happy to hear that they wanted to be macho on this spring tour,
I was also very happy to hear that I became a macho man through this spring tour,
I was really happy.
Thank you, Bertie.
What's so cute.
It's cute. It's like a bear cake. It's so cute.
Yes, I was really
I was so happy.
I'm so glad I worked so hard on it.
It was really fun.
She said she was sad that the spring tour was over.
He said he was sad that the spring tour is over.
That's right.
It was fun.
It's true, if you get too close you can only see the bangs.
I have to be careful.
I want to be friends with Emachi fans.
What?
Really, Emman!
Please be friends with my fans.
For example, if you see someone wearing orange...
I'm sure they're all nice people, so please talk to them.
Please talk to them and make friends with them.
Emachiyoshi, wait, wait!
He says he loves you because you're so sweet and fluffy.
That makes me happy. It makes you happy, too.
I'm so glad.
You're so cute!
He's so cute!I said, "Ema-chan is cute!
You said Ema-chan is cute!
I'm so happy!
Thank you so much!
I got your love letter.
I'll take it.
Shut up!
I'll be quiet.
Good night.
Emma, you're getting a lot of likes.
I didn't know...
I didn't read it.
I guessed Emma.
I couldn't say.
Thank you so much.
I'll keep reading the comments.
What was your favorite
What was your favorite part of the spring tour?
We can talk now.
Emma, can I get on with it?
Please do.
What was your favorite part?
Emma, I guess.
I don't know.
I'm so torn.
Well, I don't know.
The joint.
I liked the song choreography.
I wonder what else.
Hmmm...
But I also thought the production of the watahura effect was really cool!
Last week, I saw Emma wrote that she liked the forbidden karma of the fall.
I saw Emma-chan writing that she liked it.
I said "ahaha"...ahaha...ahaha...ahaha...ahaha...
Yama-chan from last week's "Forbidden Karma" was great!Yama-chan, last week you did a great job on Forbidden Karma.
Last week, we only did the "Fall". Were you surprised?
We did it on short notice because it was special.
Emina's first year!
Oh, that's right.
I'll give you an off shot of Emmaina's first year.
That's right.
Emaina's freshman year.
Oh, my God.
That was extremely easy for me to do.
You know...
I mean...
When I see these other commercials
I thought for sure that I couldn't speak so clearly
I would never be able to speak so clearly and clearly.
It was super easy to do.
What? How much does this T-shirt cost?
I remember now.
"Emilea's freshman year, the most fun I've had all year."
Really? Really? I'm flattered.
I'm glad you laughed, but you should have laughed a lot more.
I had a really good time.
But you know what?
I've been on a lot of expeditions and stuff,
I've been on a lot of expeditions,
I got to know Konoyu Nanaka really well,
I also got to know my sister members well,
Was it really great?
That's all I can say. Is there anything you want to ask me?
I've already said a lot on my blog,
Is there anything you guys want to ask me?
How are you?
Talk about oversleeping.
Oh, that's aggressive!
I thought you wouldn't find out about this.
Hey, Yuna.A little bit of Yuna
I saw a little bit of Nakamura Izube.
I'm totally talking.
Oh, so we talked?
Did you talk? I don't know...
We talked about this.
You talked about it with Kokoro?
Yeah, yeah, yeah. Not really.
Does everyone know about this place?
At Fukuoka Park...
I always sleep with Yuna, but she's not here
What's the matter?
Yes, I was laughing a lot...
When I woke up, I saw the time of the meeting on my phone.
I thought I couldn't do it anymore.
I couldn't think straight! It was so bad.
And when I opened the door, the manager was in front of me.
I was crying.
It was really bad.
But after that, I don't know why.
I don't know if it's a trauma alarm or what.
I sleep through the night, but now I can wake up to the sound of my alarm.
I can now wake up to the sound of my alarm.
I'm glad about that.
I'm so glad.
I'm glad.
Oh, Terumochi!
Thank you, Taco!
Octopus!
I want some octopus.
Is there anything else you want to ask me?
You all blame me.
I wish I could sleep in instead.
That's fine.
You'll get in trouble.
What would you like?What do you like?
This is so bad, it's like a shikatsun with bangs.
Thank you for watching!
Oh, oh, oh...
Oh, wow.
Oh, wow
Mr. Shimo
what's this?
Thank you very much
the one that beats like the one that beats like the one that beats
Thank you very much.
Oh, I got some kind of reproduction video.
It's fun.
Why did you start with Uchiyuki Goto?
Well, you know...
I started in Fukuoka.
Well...
A spring tour lasts a long time, doesn't it?
It goes on for a long time.
That's why...
I wonder...
Eva, when the tour is over, we'll do this... the spring tour.
I wanted to do something special, something only Eva can do.
That's when I thought...
I thought, "What's a spring tour?" And then I thought, "I can go to all the locales," and I thought, "I can go to all the locales.
And I was looking at magazines, and one of the magazines was doing a project on summer food-inspired clothing, and I thought, "This is great.
I thought it was a good idea.
I thought it would be a great idea, so I decided to dress up like the local specialty of each region.
But people made a lot of predictions, and even after the show, they asked me to do it regularly.
I was so happy to hear that many people wanted me to do this on a regular basis.
But there were a few times when I really wanted to do this food coordination.
There were times when it was difficult... I don't know what time it was... when we did the oyster coordinating... or the hedge coordinating... or the hedge coordinating...
It wasn't a hedge at all.
Oh!
Thank you, Mr. Kaven.
I wonder what they liked... erotic... what they liked...I wonder what they all liked. I wonder what they liked.
Maybe they liked white lovers.
Azunda Seek, Azunda Seek, this one, this one, this one...
Yes, that one was cute too.
Oh, Glico.
I like Glico.
I like Glico, too.
But I still like Glico, too.
Thank you, Mr. Don!
What's this?
Sparkling.
I wonder...
I'm so glad you and your son did it!
Mikuchan, Mikuchan
Full, oh, it's a penlight. Thank you very much.
I wonder what's left, well, then that, then next!
Next time, the Halo tour is really already in the back of my mind.
There's no end to what I can talk about, so I'll just put it away in my mind.
Next is the Lucky Festival.
Lucky festival was hot, hot, hot. It was hot.
I don't know what it was.
I was already dripping within a few minutes after we started playing.
I'm sweating a lot, right now.
I sweat a lot,
Last week, I was really into it,
After three songs, I was already dripping,
So, after last week's fall, I'm sorry, I'm going back to the spring tour,
I was thinking about what to do with my hair.
I was thinking about what to do with my hair since it's the last time I'm doing it,
I thought about tying my hair up,
I knew it was going to be like that.
I knew I was going to be lazy.
So, you know, at first, I thought, "I'm going to leave,
At first I thought I was going to leave it like that.
But my mom said I should do my hair a little bit,
I curled it up, and she said, well, you already got that shot, too.I wrapped it up, but I already got a shot of that too.
It was like, "Did you just take a shower? It was like, "Did you just take a shower?
And that's how it was at the Lucky Fest.
Lucky festival, you know, you know, you know,
This time, you were allowed to take pictures. Lucky festival.
So, you know,
So, you know, everyone made mentions, and I was able to see it. I could see it.
Like, "What happened to your bangs? Like, "What happened to your bangs?
What happened to your hair? Like, "What happened to your hair?
I thought, "Well, I get it now, don't I?
But I thought it would make people think that I took it that seriously.
That would be fine,
But it was a little bit, it was amazing. That was...it was soaking wet.
It was soaking wet,
Why?
But I wonder if sweating can be cured? I don't know,
Who was it again? I told someone that I sweat a lot,
I was like, "I don't know, I'm just used to it,
I don't know, maybe they are used to it, or maybe they don't want to see it on my face,
I think they got used to it, or maybe they got used to it, or maybe they stopped sweating so much on their faces.
Who was it again? You were saying.
Mikapon-san.
Thank you for the psyllium.
Mire-chan also said she sweats a lot. Yes, that's true.
Well, it's okay. I shouldn't sweat.
I really enjoyed the festival.
I guess it was the first time to hold a festival like that.
It was really fun.
But you know, everyone was pointing their cameras at me like this.
I didn't know where to look.
It was really fun!
Are you looking forward to Famirem? Of course I'm looking forward to it.
Of course you're looking forward to it. Of course you're all coming, right?
Who doesn't want to come? Well...
It's no problem if you have work, school, or other important plans.
That can't be helped. Even now, I can't go out when I haven't finished my report.I can't help it. Even now, when I haven't finished my report, I can't play with you.
But if you don't have anything, you should come.
It's Emma Ena's first time at Famien.
We want to make fun summer memories.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, I have to go.
It's great!
It's too far. I'm not sure.
It's a long way.
It's MF's first pamphlet.
But, you know...
If you can really come.
I'd love to have fun with you.
I'm really looking forward to it.
He said if you're not sure, he'll go.
Yeah.
Come on.
I'll go to the birthday party instead. Thank you.
I'm still happy.
I'd love to go to the FAMILY, but I'm sorry.
I can't help it.
It's okay. It's okay.
Wow, great! Hoji!
Thank you for the note, Nana!
Okay.
Let's talk about your birthday next time.
Let's talk.
I mean, I don't really have anything to talk about yet.
Well, first of all, please come.
I really want you to come.
I'll do my best to make your birthdays fun and make you glad you came, so please come!
I'm so glad you're coming!
Thank you for the love letter, Mr. Kaven!
I'm going to the birthday party!
What's that?What's that? That's so cute!
thank you so much!
Thank you so much.
A thousand people have seen this before I know it.
Thank you very much.
Well then...
I should say something.
I don't know...
Thank you, Ikitechi and Kuma-chan!
I'm so glad
Ema-chan!
Eh, I'm looking forward to your birthday now!
Thank you so much!
I wonder if you guys are buying tickets too.
I want one.
Oh, I want one so bad. I want one.
We're working on the schedule.
Thank you very much.
I don't want to introduce myself to anyone outside the family.
You're right, you might be there.
I'm Sakurayama from Ebisu Junior High School, a private school.
I joined as a new member last October.
I'm 15 years old, a first-year high school student.
And let's see,
I have my first birthday solo live at ZEPP Yokohama on the 13th of September!
So please come!
If you think it looks like a bit of fun
I hope you can come!
I'm in charge of honey-orange. My number is 16. Everyone says I'm waiting for pictures.
And then there's...
I'm Bob, and...
And, um...
My lips tend to get dry.
I love singing and dancing.
Chainsawing and smiling.
Yes, and I'm not a rebel.Yes, and no rebellion.
Yes, sir.
Okay, I've finished introducing myself.
I think I've gotten through to you a little bit.
Wow, H&K.
A whale? What's this? Thank you.
I'm so glad.
I'll make friends right away.
Yes, you will.
I really like talking to you.
I wonder if it's a nativity.
I've even decided what I want to wear.
I'm so excited that I wonder what I haven't decided yet.
I'm having so much fun that I wonder what I haven't decided yet.
Mikapon, I applaud you!
Thank you very much.
I can't imagine the costumes at all.
Really?
What's it like?
What? Have you decided on the photos?
Already decided.
Wow, that's great! Thank you, Mr. Moride-don and Mr. Tako!
I recommended Ebichu to my friend and she said she'd wait for the picture.
I'm so happy that you're already making such a big deal out of it.
Thank you so much!
Thank you for the heart, Shigi-san!
Thank you for your heart, Mr. Shigi. This is your chance to get a signature for the Nativity signing.
You can all get one.
And you can get the original photo.
You really should get one.
Wow, wow, paralite!
Thank you, Mr. Terumachi!
Only Mr. Emachi hasn't won yet. Oops.
This is a nice case.
Please tell us!Please tell me you'll do it.
Your first sweater will be memorable. It will be. It will be very memorable.
Oh, it's nerve-wracking, isn't it?
Mashom Ramashoosho.
Uh...
Mashom Ramashot.
Thank you very much.
It's hard to get a signature.
Oh, I see... I see...
Ehhhh...
I said "Ehhhh".
I stopped.
I'll answer some questions.
I'm sure everyone is coming to the Nativity.
I'm sure everyone has already bought their tickets, so let's have a question and answer session!
Hmmm...
Atsushi.
What did you eat today?
I had corn cakes today.
Why are you so cute?
Eeeeeeee!
I don't know.
But...
To be honest...
I don't know.
I don't think I'm that cute.
I've never thought I was that cute.
A little more...
Oh, what is it?
I'll do my best to get rid of the redness.
Wow, that was quick, quick, quick!
Today's makeup is so cute.
Thank you very much.
Today's makeup...
I did a little bit of eyeliner...I'm going to do a little bit of eyeliner.
It's the kind of makeup I like to do with a little glitter on it.
Happy birthday cover song!
Ah!
Half and half
You're even prettier than when you came in.
Thank you, thank you, thank you
I'm so happy.
Are you a gal? I wouldn't say she's a gyaru.
I think she's a little bit gal. I don't know.
I don't know.
What kind of sunscreen do you use?
What was that?
What was that? What was that?
Was it Liole?
I don't know. The blue one.
It's good.
It kind of... evens out the tone.
It doesn't burn.
It cheers me up.
Thank you very much.
I'm glad you like it.
Lucky festival.
Oh! It's gone. It's gone, it's gone, it's gone.
Oh, it's going so fast.
I don't get it.
I'll work on it.
I'm saving up for Emma Chisetto.
Thank you. I'm glad.
You work hard, Emma.
I've been thinking about you more and more lately,
Can I push?
Please push me.
I've been looking at the showroom and I'm starting to like you more and more.
Thank you very much.
I'm glad to hear you say that.I'm glad you said that.
I don't know, when I reach the ultimate happiness, I lose my vocabulary.
Well, it's always the same.
Now that it's been confirmed that there will be fresh photos
I'm going to start living with bean sprouts from today!
Sprouts? Then I'll start living on bean sprouts now, too.
Emachi.
You're early.
Something happened... something happened...
I think of Emachi as a stubborn love machine.
A machine for making hard love?
Thank you.
I'm in love with you.
Wait, wait, wait, wait...
Ema, wait a minute, something really happened.
Will you marry me, Emma? You're too cute.
She's only 16.
Let's do it in our hearts.
What the heck, let's do it in our hearts!
It was raining honey oranges on the second floor of Pacifico.
Did you see it?
I saw it.
Mmm-hmm.
But the honey oranges...
I'm getting better at finding them.
I'm definitely better at finding them.
Emma, you're my sister.
Hmm?
I want you to be my sister.
I want a big sister.
I want a big brother.
I want the older one.
Wait, wait, wait.
Emma is your first guess in life?
Hoa~Oh, no.
Oh, no!
I'm so happy.
For the first time in my life...
First time in your life?
Oh, I'm so happy!
Emma is so cute. I hope she eats a lot of food.
Of course I'll eat.
She's a growing girl.
Emma! Heart, heart, heart!
It's Ayumi.
Emma, tell us about your diet.
I'm on a diet.
Well... Emma eats breakfast and lunch.
For lunch, she eats whatever she wants, but at night she doesn't eat carbs.
Or just a little bit.
I'm going to have a special event in 20
There's a special event in March.
Until then, I'm trying to be as pretty as possible.
I'm working hard.
You should definitely eat breakfast and lunch.
Otherwise, you'll collapse.
I'll collapse. I want you to eat.
But at night?
I don't want you to eat after 8:00 p.m. And, I don't know...
I think I'd better hold off on the sweets.
I'll be at M.I.C.'s on the 23rd.
There you are.
I'll be waiting for you.
Umaibo.
What?
It went away.
The comment just flew away.
Someone said they got some Umaibo.
But that's okay.
Just some Umaibar.If it's just a Umaibar...
A little bit.
Fifty.
Mmm.
I'll give you 30 sit-ups.
It'll be gone.
I always get nervous at storytelling sessions. I always forget what I want to say.
What should I do? Well, you know, you should...
Well, you should go to Emma's first, and then you can get used to it.
After you get used to it, you can go and talk to your own guesser.
I don't know what's going on, but Emma's guess is...
When I talk to Emma, it's like I'm talking to a friend.
So you should get used to talking to people who are a little bit like friends.
Maybe you should practice so you can talk about your own work.
I don't know.
I don't know what I'd do if I lost Emma.
What? What if we lose emaci?
There's nothing to be nervous about.
Emma would be nervous.
I'm nervous about Emma because I push Emma.
You're nervous about Emma?
Yeah, I don't know.
What?
I'm not nervous. It's okay. It's okay.
I'm nervous because she's so cute.
Okay.
You're shaking when I talk to you.
Yeah, I do that sometimes.
You know...
There are kids with really shaky hands.
I don't think so.
I think that.
I think so
Not at all.
Let's have a nice, nice talk.
On the 23rd...23rd.
I'm going to the commissary.
Before going by name, you beat your heart to get into the booth.
Yuna yan.
Bang.
It's not safe. Be careful.
I'll see you today.
I'll be there to meet you.
Well, it's nice to meet you too. Please come.
What?
Oh, my God, that's great.
Satome.
Thank you so much for the tickets.
I want to meet Emma, so please sell tickets on the day of the show.
What?
You want to see Emma?
I'm so happy. I'm so happy.
That's great.
Okay, bye.
If we don't get tickets that day...
I don't know where we're going to go next.
Well, let's just call it family money.
Birthday? I don't know.
Oh, but there's that one, too. You know what?
You know what?
There's 20,000.
What?
What do you think of all the female fans?
What? Why is that?
What do you mean?
I'm so happy.
Oh, my God.
I don't care if you're a man or a woman.
If you tell me you like Emma...
I'm so happy.Glad to hear it.
I like it.
I'm glad.
I like you.
Oh yeah, and there's an Okela disco too.
It's already full of stuff! You have it in so many places!
Oh, great, great, great! Everyone's saying they love, love, love it.
I'm so happy! Thank you.
What do you want to do this summer?
What I want to do this summer is fireworks!
Well, I want at least a little bit of Kaoriko.
I want to do fireworks.
I want to see fireworks. It's just like summer.
Fireworks?
I want fireworks.
Fireworks are good, right?
I don't know...
Really?
I said "fireworks".
What was that?
It's not coming out.
What was it? What was it?
The...
The falling thing, the race thing.
What was that? What was that?
Oh, someone tell me.
Sparklers! That's it!
I want to do sparklers.
I want to do it with 10 people, and we'll see who's the first one to leave.
We'll see who's the first one left.
I'd love to do that.
What else do you want to do this summer?
Like the ocean? Well, if it's the ocean and a swimming pool, I'm a swimming pool person.
I like the ocean for taking pictures, but you know what?
I don't like fish. They scare me, you know.You know, I don't like fish. I'm afraid of them.
So, I'm a little...
Boo-boo. I really like the water slides at the pool.
Oh, I want to split a watermelon! I want to split a watermelon! Somebody want to split a watermelon...
I want to split a watermelon!
I want to split a watermelon...
Oh, suddenly I have so many things I want to do!
I want to go to a watermelon festival...
Oh, my God, everyone's been asking me to do so many things.
Let's do lots of things!
I wonder what else we can do...
If I'm around Yamachis splitting watermelons, I'll smash them.
Is the picture clear?
What? But people say it's white.
Thank you so much!
That's why I'm working so hard on my sunscreen.
I'm copying Emati, Kokorashan.
It's true.
I really do.
When I do it right.
I can say "coconachan".
I don't know why.
Why do you say "kokorashan kokorashan"?
What's wrong with you?
I got a little burned at the festival.
Lucky West was so surprised when it was hot. Emma didn't get burned.
I put a lot of paint on it.
Are you the type to talk? No, I'm not. I talk a lot.
Thank you for watching!
We're meeting BabyChu on Sunday, so try not to get burnt.
Wow!
That's great! Great!
Sure, on the 23rd, we'll all get to meet your uncle.
I'm looking forward to it!
I'm afraid my mouth will stop working halfway through.Your mouth stops working in the middle of the process.
No, really, you're right.
It doesn't work.
I can't help it now.
I got burned by the Nativity at the festival.
Of course it does.
Your hair grew long. Yes, it did.
It's grown a lot.
But you know what?
Soon I'll be in the zone where I don't like this kind of thing
I'm getting into this zone where it bounces around on my shoulders.
Oh, Jun-san!
Thank you for your pride.
You grew your bangs long too?
It's not you anymore.
My friends at school told me that today.
Oh, you grew them out already? They said it's early.
My bangs are growing really fast.
Which do you guys like better? Bob or long hair?
Both have their good points. During a long tour, long hair can be arranged in many different ways.
But a bob is also very cute, isn't it?
Ah, there's a rainbow. Thank you very much.
There are people who wear their hair long.
I like bobs. Long.
Long. Bob.
He's pretty Han-han, isn't he?
I like both of them. I'm glad.
Bob. Bob.
I like the long one.
Oh well, we're all different.
You can do a lot of different things.
Hey, I was just thinking, it says I'm going to do a survey now.
Let's do it now, for the first time.
What's that? Why did you vote for... where, how did you vote? What was it like?
What's going on?What's going on?
There's only one and two.
Which one is which?
Wait a minute.
It's hard to tell anymore.
Oh, my God.
That's great, that's great, that's great.
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
Let's do it again.
Here.
Hmm?
Oh, that's hard.
Oh, okay, okay.
I'll do one with a bob and two with long hair.
Which one do you like better?
One's a bob, two's long.
Whichever you like better.
Let's start.
I like both. I want three.
Oh, I see.
Well, I'll tell you which one I like.
I'm like...
I don't know.
Okay, one more minute.
About a minute.
Heh.
I wonder which one it is.
I really appreciate that they're both cute.
You said one is bob and two is long, right?
Okay, voting's over.
Okay.
Uh-oh.
Bob.
1... 66.1% for bob.
And 33.9% long.Long was 33.9%.
Bob.
Well, maybe it's because I have a bob now.
I wonder if they care about me.
Maybe it's just a coincidence.
I don't know.
But, you know, they're both there.
I'm glad I fell in love with long hair.
I was so shocked when I saw your bob for the first time, but I've never had it cut this long before.
I was so worried, but everyone said how cute I looked.
I'm so happy.
That's amazing. 1800 people have seen it.
I'm really grateful.
I'm so happy.
Thank you so much.
I'm so happy
I'm so happy. I'm so happy. This is my first showroom.
I'm so happy!
Asu-so many Nana-san
Thank you very much.
So everyone called me "Bobla Emma" and I was so happy to have a new nickname.
You guys are really good at making up nicknames, because Emma is the only one I've ever been called until I started this show.
I've never been called Emachie, so I was really happy to get a new nickname.
Emachie will be distributed from now on in the showroom.
We'll use the showroom.
I'm going to do it in various places.
Wait, can I take a picture with this?
Can we do a screener in the showroom? Can't we?
If it can, let's do it.
Come on, guys.
Various.
Say, "This is Mr. Sakurayama.
Say it and give him lots of money.
Give him lots of money.
Can you do it? Yes, I can! Then let's do it.
I couldn't decide on the bangs today.I couldn't decide on the bangs today.
Is there a pose you'd like me to do?
I don't know.
Let's see.
Oh, Nikko, please.
Yes, please.
Yes!
I'll make a machi-pose next time.
I want to make it. I want to make it.
Why what? What is it?
Just a little longer.
Excuse me.
Three seconds. Uh, four, five seconds.
Go ahead, go ahead, go ahead.
Hey, Nico.
You got it, right?
I think I got it.
I'm sure you got it. I'm sure you got it.
And then...
I don't know how much of this is on the camera.
This much?
Okay!
Got it!
Okay, everybody.
Put it up everywhere.
This girl...
He's talking a lot.
A lot.
She wants you to come to her birthday party.
"I want you to come to my birthday party.
She didn't move her mouth for a long time.
Please tell him.
Thank you for the penlight, Mikapong!
I'm so happy.
You know... Emachosi wants to decide on a fan name.
I really want to decide. Emma wants to decide too.I really want to decide. Emma wants to decide, too.
I know it's hard, but wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Decide. What do you like?
But you know what I've always liked about Emma?
Emmanuelle Min.
She's so cute.
Emmanuelle is cute.
Thanks.
What do you think of people who think about writing their fan names in various places when they decide to do so?
It's hard to say, isn't it?
Yes, it's cute. It sounds cute. It sounds cute. But it's hard to say.
It's like, "You shouldn't say emanumamine when you don't move your upper lip like this.
Eh?
Numachi?
But, you know, emma is somewhere...oh, but do I have to put it in?
Oh, there are so many. I don't know what to do.
Hmmm...
Numachi.
I don't know what to do.
I don't know I don't know I don't know
Emanu marmin?
I'm squeezing the floor?
NUMACHI
Let's vote on it.
Sure, sure, sure.
Wait, wait, wait.
Emma likes Emmanu Marmin first.
I thought it was cute
Emmanu Marmin and
And then I thought she was cute.
What do you think?
Emmamin. Emmamin.
Emmamin.
Emma cheese.
Emmanuelle.Emanu
Emanu Marmin.
Eh, I don't know about that for a second guys.
emanu marmin cute!
Emma cheese
MR.
I think I had something in mind when I was a research student at Stapler.
EMANUMA MAMIN
Well then...
It's a very, very slight change, but...
Emanu-mamin?
Emanu-mamin.
Emanumamine.
Eh, eh, something like, eh, wait, eh, manumamin...
Oh, I made a mistake, eh, etc., etc., etc., etc., etc., I don't know.
Tempachun...
I'm lost, me too...
You're right, it's Marmin
You must be my sister
Sure, sure, sure.
Style mane marmin.
I like emanemamin. Glad to hear it.
That's so woo.
Emma team is cute too.
So cute.
Emma team
Emma's team is so cute!
They're all so cute.
I know, I know. It's a good idea.
I really do.
Two thousand.
Thank you so much.
I'm glad.
I'm glad.Glad to hear it.
Thanks for looking.
Emcheese.
Emcheese, too. It just came to me when I was thinking about it.
Okay, well, can I have a temporary one?
Let's see...
One...
Emmanu-Mami.
Two is...
Emma cheese.
Three, Emma's team.
Hey, Honey Rangers are cute.
Well, I'll give it a shot.
One is...
Okay, just a tentative one.
Okay, one is Emma Numamine.
2 is Emma Cheese.
Three is Emma's team.
Wait, why did I put 4 in there?
Four's a little bit... So I'm gonna go with four honey rangers.
Okay, one for Emmanuelle Min.
Two, Emma Cheese.
Three for Emma Team. Four for Honey Rangers.
You guys choose. Well, I'm borrowing it just in case.
I'm borrowing it just in case. I'm trying to decide.
I think we should meet. It'll be nice.
Oh? Oh? Oh? Oh?
What? Do you think they'll fix it?
Okay, we have 32 minutes.
One minute to go.
What was that? It's just something I did once.
It's like Emma's on a cool hunting trip.
What's going on?
One for Emma Numamine, two for Emma Cheese, three for Emma Team, four for Honey Ranger.
Okay, has everyone voted yet?All right, has everybody voted yet?
Did we vote?
Five, four, three, two, one.
All right.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Ladies and gentlemen.
Are you guys seeing the results? Well, this is...
Let's see, four.
Honey Rangers.
You're the Honey Ranger now, aren't you?
But you're so cute, aren't you, Honey Ranger?
Honey Ranger for short
What the heck is that?
I wonder if they can put Emma in Honey Ranger somewhere.
But it's too long.
But Honey Ranger is so cute!
Honey Ranger...
Isn't it good?
Ogura-chan is a member of Sakuragi's army, right?
It's like a real army.
Now fans are like...
They're like Rangers.
My mom's looking at the papers now, too.
She says she might like the Honey Rangers, too.
The Honey Rangers are cute.
Honey...
Hey, you're really cute, but Honey Ranger
Honey Rangers
It's too long, but it's cute.
I don't know if I need to put a picture in there.
I wonder if they'll be interested in it.
I wonder if they'll be curious about what a Honey Ranger is.
Thank you for watching!
Oh, so Emma is the captain.
I see.I see.
Emma Sentai Honey Ranger
It's getting interesting now, isn't it?
Well, let's make it temporary.
Let's call them Honey Rangers.
Everyone seems to like it.
Maybe.
What do you think? Gentlemen.
Honey Rangers.
So, if you wrote Honey Ranger...
I'm...
That club member...
I don't know what to call it.
And the squadron
Honey
Thank you for watching
Emma, Emma, Hani, Emma
Emma Emma Hani Hani
Hanii Ranger Hanii Hanii
Ha ni yi ha ni yi
That's a tough one.
Looks like a unit.
Gentlemen.
If I write "Honey Ranger," then...
You're all going to be
You're all going to be Honey Ranger units.
Oh!
A unit of honey ranger.
"Honeylé" is a nice abbreviation.
Honeylé.
Honey.
It says I'm coming home in a hurry. I'm glad.
Hanire? Hanire, hanire. Hanire for short.
I'm Honey Ranger.
Hey, hey...
I've got it all together again...Putting it all together again...
I think Honey Ranger should be Honey Ranger.
Really?
Honey Ranger is...
Honey Rangers.
Can I put the hashtag Honey Ranger?
Put it on. Put it on.
Please put it on.
Now that's funny cherry blossom sisters, the Legion and the Rangers are too powerful.
No doubt.
Well, let's just say I'm still writing.
I'm sure I'll get around to it.
I wish I could think about it more slowly.
I'll take it home.
It'd be cute if we decided on the details.
So, I'll definitely decide on it at your birthday.
I promise.
Oh, no!
So many things...
But I think Honey Ranger is really cute!
Please, please, by all means...
You know, you can borrow some of my cool stuff and write about it
I mean, please write about all kinds of things!
So, it's a little bit cuckoo-ish
Um, my
Now that we have decided on the names of all the Oshisans
I think that's all for today.
That was a fast one hour!
It went by so fast, and, and, and, and, and, and...
Thank you for 2000 people.
Thank you so much!
Thank you very much.
So...
You know, like I always do.
Top of the listTop
I would like to read your comments.
First, you always said this from the bottom.
13th place
Thank you Don in the forest!
Next, 12th place
Thank you, Satome-san!
Eleventh place
11th place
Thank you, Jun!
Sorry, it's so close!
10th place
Thank you, Shimo!
19th, Nana-san SOLA-san
Thank you, KORORI!
7th, Terumuchi, thank you!
6th place, Kashihige-san Thank you very much!
5th place, Mr. OOTORO, thank you!
4th place, MIKAPON, thank you very much!
3rd place, Keibun, thank you!
2nd place, Taka, thank you very much!
1st place, Baachii, thank you very much!
Thank you all very much for everything today!
See you next time on 23rd.
See you next 23rd.
I'll be back next time on the 23rd.
We're going to have a birthday party at our house.
Please come and visit us!
That's all I have to say.
Bye bye!
Thank you.
Bye bye.